我们合成的URL和从服务器获取的JSON字符串
The URL that we built looks good and the JSON
看上去都不错。不过这字符串还是挺长的
string from the server also looks good. However, it still is
让我们仔细看看
one long string. Let's look at it more carefully to see
我们应该从中提取什么数据
what data we should extract from it. In order to make
为了更直观地观察从服务器取回的字符串
sense of the string that comes back from the server, we
我们可以用JSON格式化器或者说是美化器来处理下
can put it through a JSON formatter or a JSON prettifier.
如果你用Google搜索下，你可以找到
If you Google for those terms, you'll be able to find
一些有用的工具，例如这个。我们把查询结果
a helpful tool such as this one. Here, we pasted the
粘贴到这里。然后它输出一个
result of the web query. Then, it formatted the output for
格式化过的JSON
us showing us the hierarchy of these elements. Now based on
现在，基于之前给出的Sunshine的框架图
the wireframes that you saw for the Sunshine app, can you
你能告诉我们这里哪些叶节点是我们所想要的吗？
tell us which of these leaf nodes we care about extracting?
虽然我们需要从父节点经过
Even though we will have to traverse through parent nodes, for
但是为了下一屏幕的小测验
the purposes of the quiz on the next screen, we're just
我们只关注这些叶节点。在下面选择你认为
looking at the leaf nodes. Make your selections below on which
我们需要在预报列表中显示的属性
attributes we'll need in order to display the list of forecasts